A Guide to the Minutes of the Board of Commissioners of the Virginia Housing Development Authority, 1973-2008
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Minutes of the Board of Commissioners of the Virginia Housing Development Authority, 1973-2008
The Library of Virginia
43807, 43860, 43937, 43974, 44023, 44224, 51287, 51420
51 cu. ft. (51 boxes)
Virginia Housing Development Authority
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred on 11 June 2008 from the Virginia Housing Development Authority, Richmond, VA [Acc. 43807].
Transferred on 2 July 2008 from the Virginia Housing Development Authority, Richmond, VA [Acc. 43860].
Transferred on 26 August 2008 from the Virginia Housing Development Authority, Richmond, VA [Acc. 43937].
Transferred on 20 October 2008 from the Virginia Housing Development Authority, Richmond, VA [Acc. 43974].
Transferred on 25 November 2008 from the Virginia Housing Development Authority, Richmond, VA [Acc. 44023].
Transferred on 15 April 2009 from the Virginia Housing Development Authority, Richmond, VA [Acc. 44244].
Transferred on 15 April 2014 from the Virginia Housing Development Authority, Richmond, VA [Acc. 51287].
Transferred on 17 October 2014 from the Virginia Housing Development Authority, Richmond, VA [Acc. 51420].
Biographical Information
The Virginia Housing Development Authority (VHDA) is the state's mortgage finance agency. Created in 1972 by the Virginia General Assembly, its mission is to help Virginians with low and moderate income levels attain quality, affordable housing. VHDA is a quasi-government agency, and as such, the governor appoints its eleven-member Board of Commissioners. However, the authority is self-supporting and does not use tax dollars to fund its lending programs.
Scope and Content
Meeting minutes and other meeting materials and related attachments, 1973-2008, from the Board of Commissioner's of the Virginia Housing Authority.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged by accession number into eight (8) series:
Series I: Minutes, 1973-1982 [Acc. 43807]
Series II: Minutes, 1978-1979 [Acc. 43860]
Series III: Minutes, 1977 [Acc. 43937]
Series IV: Minutes, 1983-1995 [Acc. 43974]
Series V: Minutes, 1987-2003 [Acc. 44023]
Series VI: Minutes, 1981-2000 [Acc. 44224]
Series VII: Minutes, 2004-2007 [Acc. 51287]; and
Series VIII: Minutes, 1984-2008 [Acc. 51420].
Contents List
- Series I: Minutes, 1973-1982 [Acc. 43807], Extent: 9 cu. ft. (9 boxes). (Box 1-9)
  - Minutes, 1973-1975 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Minutes, 1980 January-June (Box 3)
  - Minutes, 1980 July-December (Box 4)
  - Minutes, 1981 January-July (Box 5)
  - Minutes, 1981 August-December (Box 6)
  - Minutes, 1982 January-April (Box 7)
  - Minutes, 1982 May-August (Box 8)
  - Minutes, 1982 September-December (Box 9)
- Series II: Minutes, 1978-1979 [Acc. 43860], Extent: 2 cu. ft. (2 boxes). (Box 1-2)
  - Minutes, 1978 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 1979 (Box 2)
- Series III: Minutes, 1977 May-December [Acc. 43937], Extent: 1 cu. ft. (1 boxes). (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 1977 May-December (Box 1)
- Series IV: Minutes, 1983-1995 [Acc. 43974], Extent: 14 cu. ft. (14 boxes). (Box 1-14)
  - Minutes, 1983 January-1984 February (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 1984 March-December (Box 2)
  - Minutes, 1985 (Box 3)
  - Minutes, 1986 (Box 4)
  - Minutes, 1987 January-July (Box 5)
  - Minutes, 1987 August-December (Box 6)
  - Minutes, 1988 January-June (Box 7)
  - Minutes, 1988 July-December (Box 8)
  - Minutes, 1989 (Box 9)
  - Minutes, 1990 (Box 10)
  - Minutes, 1993 (Box 11)
  - Minutes, 1994 (Box 12)
  - Minutes, 1995 January-July (Box 23)
  - Minutes, 1995 August-December (Box 14)
- Series V: Minutes, 1987-2003 [Acc. 44023], Extent: 15 cu. ft. (15 boxes). (Box 1-15)
  - Minutes, 1987 October; 1990 September; 1991 January-June (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 1991 July-December (Box 2)
  - Minutes, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Minutes, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Minutes, 1997 January-June (Box 5)
  - Minutes, 1997 July-December (Box 6)
  - Minutes, 1998 January-July (Box 7)
  - Minutes, 1998 August-December (Box 8)
  - Minutes, 1999 January-May (Box 9)
  - Minutes, 1999 June-December (Box 10)
  - Minutes, 2000 January-July (Box 11)
  - Minutes, 2000 August-December (Box 12)
  - Minutes, 2001 (Box 13)
  - Minutes, 2002 (Box 14)
  - Minutes, 2003 (Box 15)
- Series VI: Minutes, 1981-2000 [Acc. 44224], Extent: 7 cu. ft. (7 boxes). (Box 1-7)
  - Minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 1983-1985 (Box 2)
  - Minutes, 1986-1988 (Box 3)
  - Minutes, 1989-1991 (Box 4)
  - Minutes, 1993 (Box 5)
  - Minutes, 1994-2000 (Box 6)
  - Minutes, 1996 (Box 7)
- Series VII: Minutes, 2004-2007 [Acc. 51287], Extent: 2 cu. ft. (2 boxes). (Box 1-2)
  - Minutes, 2004-2005 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 2006-2007 (Box 2)
- Series VIII: Minutes, 1984-2008 [Acc. 51420], Extent: 1 cu. ft. (1 box). (Box 1)
  - Board meeting notices and certification of posting, 1984-2008 (Box 1)